# ANDRII SUSHKET

andy.sushket@gmail.com | +352661527603 | Luxembourg LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/andrii-sushket

## **SUMMARY**

Passionate **WebGL (Three.js)** Frontend Developer with 7 years of experience. Excited about 3D challenges and problem-solving. Formerly at Logivations, shaping 3D warehouse solutions. Currently contributing to solar panel visualization at Svitla Systems. Working on a new visualization core for solar panels on roofs using various tools. Experienced in JS, TS, React, Redux, Three,js, GLSL, Webpack, and more. An adaptable team player. Respecting deadlines and minimizing tech debt. Eager to expand 3D knowledge and in the future dive into C++ and Unreal Engine. Future-focused and ready for new adventures. I am open to collaborations, networking, and discussions on all things tech.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Senior Frontend Developer | Svitla Systems Inc. - Remote

10/2021 - Current

Stack: JavaScript, Three.js, React, Redux, Saga, Node.js, Webpack, SASS, MongoDB, WebSocket, Jest.

- Developed a new rendering engine using Three.js, resulting in a tenfold increase in performance.
- Implemented synchronization between 3D objects and Google Maps tiles, ensuring interaction.
- Built-in support for quadtrees to optimize interactive operations such as intersection and selection.
- Optimized processes at the shader level to improve rendering performance.

**3D Developer** | Logivations - Remote/Office, Ukraine

10/2017 - 10/2021

Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, Three.js, React, Redux, Reflux, Backbone, LESS, Socket.io, Webpack.

- Developed real-time visualizations, collaborating with ML for object detection and management.
- Revamped product packaging visualization, improving functionality and performance.
- Developed support for importing animated models, ensuring JSON data storage in the database.

Frontend Developer | ABC Hosting - Remote

03/2017 - 10/2017

Stack: JavaScript, PHP, jQuery, HTML, and CSS.

- Engineered templates for enhanced hosting functionality, optimizing user experience.
- Contributed to website animations to enrich user engagement and experience.

### **EDUCATION**

**Engineer Specialist:** Radio communication, broadcasting and television 2009 - 2016

Polytechnic University | Lviv/Ukraine

HTML\CSS, JavaScript, JavaScript Advanced Courses 2016

Logos | Lviv/Ukraine

Three.is, Shaders, Post-processing, Blender, R3F Course 2023

Three.js Journey | Online

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Upper intermediate Ukrainian Native Russian Native